Jiun, Bae

Student. Interested in Artificial Intelligence and Data Science.

Have experienced handling huge data for analyze and configure distributed processing system using docker or cloud instances.

Studying machine learning and publish services using computer vision and NLP.

blog.maydev.org github.com/MaybeS linkedin.com/in/maydev Seoul, Korea maytryark@gmail.com +82 10 3804 4496

Education

Computer Engineering @ Yonsei Univ. (2014.03 ~ 2015)

Computer Science and Engineering @ Hanyang Univ. (2015.03 ~)

Experience

Participate algorithm competitions

Practice Kaggle competitions

Contribute open source project <u>CS231n Translation</u>, <u>Naver</u>

ALOHA: Hanyang Univ. Algorithm Club (2015.03 -)

- Host on Hanyang Univ. algorithm competition

ICEWALL: Hanyang Univ. Student Cert. (2015.03 -)

- Web site penetration test

Developer at Perigee Rocket LLC. (2015.03 – 2018.06)

- Develop flight software and firmwares

Mentee at <u>SW Maestro</u> (2016.06 – 2017.07)

Internship at <u>mapianist</u> (2017.07 - 2017.08)

- Optical music sheet recognition

Overseas training at <u>Draper Ulniv.</u> (2017.08 – 2017.09)

Internship at Computer Vison Lab in Hanyang Univ. (2017.09 -)

- Single object tracking using OTB dataset
- Multi object tracking based on MDNet

Internship at Naver Webtoon Research (2018.09 -)

Achievements ACM ICPC 16th prize (Daejeon regional)

Google Machine Learning Challenge 2017 5th prize

Projects

Object tracking (MAT4015 @ Hanyang Univ.)

Implement Mean shift object tracking (C++)

- Dynamic search area with auto scaling
- Real-time back projection

Deep Check (SW Maestro)

Face detection (Improve of YOLO, Python)

- Modify hyper parameters (increase grid size)
- Image Argumentation
- Ensemble multiple models
- Concatenation search area

App (React-Native)

API server (Flask, Ruby on Rails)

Memento (SW Maestro)

Crawling news and web-documents (Scrapy, Python)

- Construct distributed processing system (docker)
- Prevent duplicate collection using ElasticSearch

Natural Language Processing

- Morphological analysis (konlpy with custom dictionary)
- Using extracted stop words from crawled data

- Vector embedding with doc2vec

Clustering word vector

- Ensemble hierarchy cluster, k-mean, ···

Named Entity Recognition

MariaDB Scalable Lock Manager (ITE4065 @ Hanyang Univ.)

Latch-Free lock management (C/C++)

- Atomic lock insertion, deletion

Reusable object pool with garbage collector

Increase select query performance more than 40%

Skills Languages

Python, C/C++, JAVA, C#, JS Haskell, R, Ruby Use for commercial service

Try for personal projects

Database

MySQL, Elasticsearch